Daniel Rosenbaum

3139 Ellenwood Drive Fairfax VA 22031 703-615-2053

Drosenbaum5@gmail.com

Professional Profile:

Motivated and customer service-oriented System/Network Administrator, recognized for strong interpersonal communication and effective problem-solving skills. Hands on experience implementing, upgrading, and maintaining various small to medium sized businesses' IT infrastructure to meet customer's needs. Actively working towards attaining CompTIA Certifications and furthering higher education.

Summary of Skills:

- Windows Server 2008 R2/2012 R2/2016
- Windows 7/8/10
- MS Office Suite/Office 365
- AD DS
- DNS
- **DHCP**
- **Group Policy**

- System Installation, Configuration, and Upgrading
- Hardware/Software installation, troubleshooting and configuration
- User Training and Technical Support
- AirWatch MDM
- Installing, customizing, and running virtual machines (VMware vSphere)

Professional Experience:

System/Network Administrator **BoltMSP**

2016- Present

- Configure, deploy, upgrade and maintain servers, switches, firewalls, desktops, laptops, iPads, and mobile devices
- Provide Tier 1 and 2 remote/on-site support for 50 small and medium sized businesses. Use TruMethods MSP framework to evaluate infrastructure, reduce ticket counts, and resolve issues pro-actively
- Ensure quality education when training new Tier 1 help desk employees
- Build networking labs for training purposes and to ensure software and hardware was compatible before being introduced to production environments
- Modernize and sustain IT infrastructure of healthcare facility with over 350 employees
- Provide on-site support for healthcare facility on weekdays and remote support on evenings and weekends
- Worked with C level executives, IT Director, and HR Director of healthcare facility to implement workflow policies, employee technical training, IT Policy, and inventory systems

Bartender/Server 2013-2016

Pazzo Pomodoro

- Accommodated diverse clientele and resolved customer complaints
- Recommended Menu items and drinks based on customer preferences
- Provided top class customer service, as indicated by positive feedback and reviews
- Maintained relationships with regular clientele to gain repeat business
- Maintained a positive working relationship with co-workers and management

Assistant Manager, Gaming Department

2010-2011

- **Best Buy**
 - Reported to direct manager and store manager regarding sales numbers and marketing
 - Maintained high-level product knowledge. Received recognition for conveying product features and benefits, as indicated in customer surveys
 - Managed all retail duties, including cashier work, restocking, and customer care

Education: Currently Working On

Associate of Applied Science: Cyber Security

Northern Virginia Community College - Annandale VA, United States 2016-Present

CSC, Network Administration

Northern Virginia Community College - Annandale, VA, United States 2016-Present

CSC, Cyber Security

Northern Virginia Community College - Annandale, VA, United States 2016-2018